American Scholar Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: General Editorial File, 1931-1988 (Box II-1-11)
  - 1979-1980
    - General correspondence, 1979-1980
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1979
      - Winter, 1979
      - Spring, 1979-1980
      - Summer, 1980
    - Review copies requested, 1979-1980
  - 1980-1981
    - Epstein, Joseph, 1980
    - General correspondence, 1980-1981
    - Personnel, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box II:7)
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1980
      - Winter, 1980
      - Spring, 1980
      - Summer, 1980-1981
    - Review copies requested, 1980-1981, (2 folders)
  - 1981-1982
    - Epstein, Joseph, 1981
    - General correspondence, 1981-1982
    - Personnel
      - 1981
      - 1982 (Box II:8)
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1981
      - Winter, 1981
      - Spring, 1981-1982
      - Summer, 1981-1982
    - Review copies requested
      - Epstein, Joseph, 1981-1982
      - General, 1981-1982
  - 1982-1983
    - Budget request, 1982-1983
    - General correspondence, 1982-1983
    - Personnel, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
    - "The Reader Replies" (Box II:9)
      - Autumn, 1982
      - Winter, 1982
      - Spring, 1982-1983
      - Summer, 1983
    - Review copies requested
      - Epstein, Joseph, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
      - General, 1982-1983
  - 1983-1984
    - Budget, 1984
    - General correspondence, 1983-1984
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1983
      - Winter, 1983
      - Spring, 1982-1984
      - Summer, 1983-1984, (2 folders)
    - Review copies requested
      - Epstein, Joseph
        - 1983
        - 1984 (Box II:10)
      - General, 1983-1984
  - 1984-1985
    - Correspondence
      - Epstein, Joseph, 1984-1985
      - General, 1984-1985
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1984
      - Spring, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
      - Summer, 1984-1985
  - 1985-1986
    - General correspondence, 1985-1986
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1985
      - Winter, 1985
      - Spring, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
      - Summer, 1984-1986
  - 1986-1987 (Box II:11)
    - General correspondence, 1986-1987
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1986-1987
      - Winter, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
      - Spring, 1986
      - Summer, 1986-1987
  - 1987-1988
    - General correspondence, 1987-1988
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1986-1987
      - Winter, 1987
      - Spring, 1987-1988
      - Summer, 1987-1988, (2 folders)
- Part II: Author File, 1932-1988 (Box II:11-63)
  Correspondence with authors submitting articles and poems to the American Scholar, including those which were rejected. Also letters from the editors soliciting articles.
  - Pre-1970 (Box II:11)
    - D-R, 1932
    - A-Z, 1934-1970, (9 folders) (Box II:12)
  - 1971-1972
    - Ab-Bl, 1971-1972, (3 folders)
    - Bo-Gu, 1969-1972, (8 folders) (Box II:13)
    - Hae-Mat, 1970-1972, (9 folders) (Box II:14)
    - May-Syk, 1967-1972, (8 folders) (Box II:15)
    - T-Z, 1969-1972, (5 folders) (Box II:16)
  - 1972-1973, (6 folders)
  - 1974-1975, C, R, 1975
  - 1976-1977 (Box II:17)
    - A-E, 1974-1977, (9 folders)
    - Fai-Kop, 1971-1977, (10 folders) (Box II:18)
    - Kor-Rix, 1964-1977, (9 folders) (Box II:19)
    - Ro-Wa, 1970-1977, (9 folders) (Box II:20)
    - We-Zu, 1966-1977, (3 folders) (Box II:21)
  - 1977-1978
    - Ac-De, 1976-1978, (7 folders)
    - Di-Hu, 1975-1978, (10 folders) (Box II:22)
    - J-Q, 1974-1978, (10 folders) (Box II:23)
    - Ra-Wh, 1975-1978, (10 folders) (Box II:24)
    - Wi-Zy, 1976-1978, (2 folders) (Box II:25)
  - 1978-1979
    - A-D, 1975-1979, (7 folders)
    - Eb-Le, 1975-1979, (12 folders) (Box II:26)
    - Lien-Stei, 1976-1979, (10 folders) (Box II:27)
    - Stel-Zwei, 1976-1979, (5 folders) (Box II:28)
  - 1979-1980
    - A-B, 1977-1980, (5 folders)
    - Cad-Hit, 1978-1980, (8 folders) (Box II:29)
    - Hoc-Owe, 1976-1980, (10 folders) (Box II:30)
    - P-W, 1976-1980, (10 folders) (Box II:31)
    - Y-Z, 1979-1980 (Box II:32)
  - 1980-1981
    - A-C, 1976-1981, (9 folders)
    - D-H, 1976-1981, (9 folders) (Box II:33)
    - I-O, 1976-1981, (10 folders) (Box II:34)
    - Pai-Ste, 1979-1981, (10 folders) (Box II:35)
    - Sto-Zwe, 1976-1981, (8 folders) (Box II:36)
  - 1981-1982
    - Abb-Blu, 1973-1982, (3 folders)
    - Bob-Her, 1972-1982, (9 folders) (Box II:37)
    - Hic-Mus, 1968-1982, (9 folders) (Box II:38)
    - N-V, 1974-1982, (9 folders) (Box II:39)
    - W-Z, 1979-1982, (3 folders) (Box II:40)
  - 1982-1983
    - A-D, 1978-1983, (7 folders)
    - Ear-Kel, 1980-1983, (8 folders) (Box II:41)
    - Ken-Sex, 1977-1983, (8 folders) (Box II:42)
    - Sha-Zwe, 1977-1983, (7 folders) (Box II:43)
  - 1983-1984
    - Aar-Blu, 1978-1984, (3 folders)
    - Bob-Giv, 1980-1984, (9 folders) (Box II:44)
  - 1983-1984 (Box II:45)
    - Gla-Mik, 1975-1984, (10 folders)
    - Mil-Tyl, 1980-1984, (10 folders) (Box II:46)
    - U-Z, 1983-1984, (4 folders) (Box II:47)
  - 1984-1985
    - A-B, 1982-1985, (5 folders)
    - Ca-Hu, 1975-1985, (10 folders) (Box II:48)
    - I-O, 1981-1985, (11 folders) (Box II:49)
    - Pai-Wel, 1981-1985, (10 folders) (Box II:50)
    - Wer-Zuc, 1982-1985, (2 folders) (Box II:51)
  - 1985-1986
    - A-C, 1982-1986, (7 folders)
    - Da-Ke, 1983-1986, (8 folders) (Box II:52)
    - Kie-Rid, 1981-1986, (10 folders) (Box II:53)
    - Rif-Wet, 1984-1986, (9 folders) (Box II:54)
    - Wh-Zy, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box II:55)
  - 1986-1987
    - A-E, 1983-1987, (7 folders)
    - F-K, 1982-1987, (9 folders) (Box II:56)
    - L-R, 1983-1987, (10 folders) (Box II:57)
    - S-W, 1982-1987, (9 folders) (Box II:58)
    - Y-Z, 1986-1987 (Box II:59)
  - 1987-1988
    - A-D, 1982-1988, (9 folders)
    - Eas-Kel, 1982-1988, (8 folders) (Box II:60)
    - Kem-Mom, 1983-1988, (8 folders) (Box II:61)
    - Mon-Rye, 1981-1988, (10 folders) (Box II:62)
    - S-Z, 1981-1988, (9 folders) (Box II:63)
- Part II: Miscellany, 1957-1986 (Box II:63-64)
  Correspondence regarding articles and poems accepted by the American Scholar, but never published. Includes Japanese art presented to editor Hiram Haydn.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Articles and poems purchased, not used (Box II:63)
    - Berkeley, Edmund C., 1962
    - General, 1960-1983 (Box II:64)
    - Lorenz, Clarissa, 1973-1976
  - Japanese artwork, 1957
  - Poetry solicited, 1974-1986, (2 folders)
- Part III: Correspondence, 1988-2006 (Box III:1-97)
  Correspondence with authors and general correspondence with readers, printers, and business contacts.
  Arranged chronologically by the years spanning publication of each volume of the magazine and thereunder in separate author and general correspondence files. Author correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of author. Lists of authors are included for the period 2001-2006. General correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of person, topic, or type of material.
  - 1988-1989 (Box III:1)
    - Authors
      - A-E, (11 folders)
      - F-K, (9 folders) (Box III:2)
      - L-R, (12 folders) (Box III:3)
      - S-W, (9 folders) (Box III:4)
      - X-Z (Box III:5)
    - General
      - “A-Z” miscellaneous
      - Nieman, Tom
      - Promotion
      - Reader replies, (4 folders)
      - William Byrd Press, (3 folders)
  - 1989-1990 (Box III:6)
    - Authors
      - A-C, (8 folders)
      - D-G, (7 folders) (Box III:7)
      - H, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:8)
      - I-L, (6 folders)
      - M, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:9)
      - N-R, (7 folders)
      - S, (2 folders) (Box III:10)
      - T-Z, (8 folders)
    - General
      - “A-Z” miscellaneous
      - Nieman, Tom
      - Reader replies, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:11)
  - 1990-1991
    - Authors
      - A-C, (7 folders)
      - D-H, (9 folders) (Box III:12)
      - I-M, (11 folders) (Box III:13)
      - N-R, (7 folders) (Box III:14)
      - S, (3 folders) (Box III:15)
      - T-Z, (7 folders)
    - General
      - “A-Z” miscellaneous
      - Nieman, Tom
      - Ravitch, Diane, (2 folders)
      - Reader replies, (4 folders) (Box III:16)
  - 1991-1992
    - Authors
      - A, (2 folders)
      - B, (2 folders) (Box III:17)
      - C-E, (6 folders)
      - F, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:18)
      - G-H, (8 folders)
      - I-L, (8 folders) (Box III:19)
      - M, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:20)
      - N-Q, (5 folders)
      - R, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:21)
      - S-U, (7 folders)
      - V-Z, (5 folders) (Box III:22)
    - General
      - “A-Z” miscellaneous
      - Nieman, Tom
      - Reader replies, (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:23)
  - 1992-1993
    - Authors
      - A, (2 folders)
      - B, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:24)
      - C-F, (8 folders)
      - G-H, (8 folders) (Box III:25)
      - I -L, (8 folders) (Box III:26)
      - M (Box III:27)
        - Miscellaneous, (6 folders)
        - Moynihan, Daniel P.
      - N-O, (2 folders)
      - P-R, (7 folders) (Box III:28)
      - S, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:29)
      - T-Z, (6 folders)
    - General (Box III:30)
      - Ravitch, Diane, (2 folders)
      - Reader replies, (3 folders)
  - 1993-1994
    - Authors
      - A
      - B, (1 folder) (Box III:31)
      - C-F, (7 folders)
      - G-J, (7 folders) (Box III:32)
      - K, (1 folder) (Box III:33)
      - L-M, (7 folders)
      - N-R, (10 folders) (Box III:34)
      - S, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box III:35)
      - T-Z, (6 folders)
    - General (Box III:36)
      - Books
      - Controversy
      - Reader replies, (3 folders)
      - Subscriber comments
  - 1994-1995
    - Authors
      - A, (2 folders)
      - B, (2 folders) (Box III:37)
      - C-D, (5 folders)
      - E, (1 folder) (Box III:38)
      - F-I, (9 folders)
      - J-L, (6 folders) (Box III:39)
      - M, (2 folders) (Box III:40)
      - N-R, (8 folders)
      - S-V, (8 folders) (Box III:41)
      - W, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:42)
      - X-Z, (3 folders)
    - General
      - Binding problems
      - Reader replies, (6 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:43)
      - Subscriber comments
  - 1995-1996
    - Authors
      - A, (2 folders)
      - B, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:44)
      - C-E, (6 folders)
      - F-G, (6 folders) (Box III:45)
      - H, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:46)
      - I-L, (6 folders)
      - M, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box III:47)
      - N-Q, (5 folders)
      - R, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:48)
      - S, (6 folders)
      - T-Z, (8 folders) (Box III:49)
    - General
      - Lancaster Press
        - Bills
        - Correspondence
        - Quotations
  - 1996-1997
    - Authors
      - A
      - B, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box III:50)
      - C-D, (4 folders)
      - E (Box III:51)
      - F
        - Forum on American history, (2 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - G, (2 folders)
      - H, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:52)
      - I-L, (6 folders)
      - M, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:53)
      - N-R, (7 folders)
      - S, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box III:54)
      - T-Z, (6 folders)
    - General (Box III:55)
      - Fax cover sheets
      - Lancaster Press
        - Bills
        - Correspondence
        - Quotations
      - Reader replies, (4 folders)
      - Tearsheets
  - 1997-1998 (Box III:56)
    - Authors
      - A-E, (9 folders)
      - F-G, (5 folders) (Box III:57)
      - H, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:58)
      - I- L, (7 folders)
      - M, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box III:59)
      - N-R, (7 folders)
      - S, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box III:60)
      - T-W, (6 folders)
      - X-Z (Box III:61)
    - General
      - Reader replies, (10 folders); (4 folders) (Box III:62)
  - 1998-1999
    - Authors
      - A-B, (6 folders)
      - C-E, (7 folders) (Box III:63)
      - F-H, (8 folders) (Box III:64)
      - I-L, (8 folders) (Box III:65)
      - M, (3 folders) (Box III:66)
      - N-Q, (5 folders)
      - R, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:67)
      - S, (6 folders)
      - T-Z, (9 folders) (Box III:68)
    - General
      - Kazin, Alfred, memorial
      - Lancaster Press (Box III:69)
        - Bills
        - Correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Reader replies, (3 folders)
      - Tearsheets, (2 folders)
  - 2001-2002 (Box III:70)
    - Authors
      - List of authors
      - A-B, (7 folders)
      - C
        - (1 folder), (3 folders) (Box III:71)
      - D-F, (7 folders)
      - G-I, (10 folders) (Box III:72)
      - J-L, (8 folders) (Box III:73)
      - M-O, (9 folders) (Box III:74)
      - P-R, (7 folders) (Box III:75)
      - S, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box III:76)
      - T
      - U-Z, (6 folders) (Box III:77)
  - 2002-2003
    - Authors
      - List of authors
      - A, (3 folders)
      - B, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:78)
      - C-D, (6 folders)
      - E-I, (10 folders) (Box III:79)
      - J-L, (6 folders) (Box III:80)
      - M, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:81)
      - N-R, (8 folders)
      - S, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:82)
      - T-Z, (7 folders)
  - 2003-2004
    - Authors
      - List of authors
      - A, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:83)
      - B, (5 folders)
      - C, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:84)
      - D-F, (8 folders)
      - G-J, (11 folders) (Box III:85)
      - K-M, (14 folders) (Box III:86)
      - N-R, (7 folders) (Box III:87)
      - S, (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box III:88)
      - T-Z, (8 folders)
  - 2004-2005
    - Authors
      - List of authors
      - A, (3 folders)
      - B-C, (12 folders) (Box III:89)
      - D-H, (10 folders) (Box III:90)
      - I-O, (13 folders) (Box III:91)
      - P-T, (10 folders) (Box III:92)
      - U-Z, (6 folders) (Box III:93)
  - 2005-2006
    - Authors
      - List of authors
      - A-B, (4 folders)
      - C-G, (10 folders) (Box III:94)
      - H-L, (11 folders) (Box III:95)
      - M, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:96)
      - N-R, (6 folders)
      - S, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:97)
      - T-Z, (8 folders)
- Part III: Production File, 1984-2006 (Box III:98-199)
  Original manuscripts, edited drafts, and author's galleys of articles, book reviews, essays, poetry, and other departments of the magazine, along with editorial correspondence.
  Arranged by date of publication and thereunder alphabetically by type of document or component of the magazine.
  - 1984 (vol. 53) (Box III:98)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Summer (Box III:99)
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:100)
  - 1985 (vol. 54)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Spring (Box III:101)
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:102)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
  - 1986 (vol. 55)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:103)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Summer (Box III:104)
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:105)
  - 1987 (vol. 56)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:106)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1988 (vol. 57) (Box III:107)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:108)
  - 1989 (vol. 58)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Spring (Box III:109)
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:110)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1990 (vol. 59) (Box III:111)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:112)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Autumn (Box III:113)
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1991 (vol. 60)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:114)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Summer (Box III:115)
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:116)
  - 1992 (vol. 61)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Spring (Box III:117)
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:118)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1993 (vol. 62) (Box III:119)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (3 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (4 folders) (Box III:120)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (5 folders) (Box III:121)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders) (Box III:122)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1994 (vol. 63)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (5 folders) (Box III:123)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (5 folders) (Box III:124)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:125)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box III:126)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1995 (vol. 64)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box III:127)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders) (Box III:128)
    - Spring
      - Author's galleys, (5 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:129)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box III:130)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:131)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
  - 1996 (vol. 65) (Box III:132)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (5 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Spring (Box III:133)
      - Author's galleys, (6 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders) (Box III:134)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (3 folders) (Box III:135)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Autumn (Box III:136)
      - Author's galleys, (5 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box III:137)
  - 1997 (vol. 66)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Spring (Box III:138)
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Summer
      - Author's galleys, (2 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders) (Box III:139)
    - Autumn
      - Author's galleys, (3 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (2 folders)
  - 1998 (vol. 67) (Box III:140)
    - Winter
      - Author's galleys, (4 folders)
      - Original manuscripts, (3 folders)
    - Spring (Box III:141)
      - Articles, (7 folders)
      - Departments, (2 folders) (Box III:142)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
    - Summer
      - Articles, (2 folders)
      - Books
      - Departments and miscellany
      - Poetry (Box III:143)
      - Reader replies
    - Autumn
      - Articles, (3 folders)
      - Books
      - Departments, (2 folders) (Box III:144)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
  - 1999 (vol. 68)
    - Winter
      - Articles, (9 folders); (6 folders) (Box III:145)
      - Books, (2 folders)
      - Departments, (2 folders) (Box III:146)
      - Dummy
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies, (3 folders)
    - Spring
      - Articles, (2 folders); (9 folders) (Box III:147)
      - Books (Box III:148)
      - Departments, (2 folders)
      - Dummy
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies, (2 folders)
    - Summer (Box III:149)
      - Articles, (10 folders)
      - Books (Box III:150)
      - Departments, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies, (3 folders)
    - Autumn (Box III:151)
      - Articles, (8 folders)
      - Books, (2 folders) (Box III:152)
      - Departments, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies, (2 folders)
  - 2000 (vol. 69) (Box III:153)
    - Winter
      - Articles, (10 folders)
      - Books
      - Departments (Box III:154)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
    - Spring
      - Articles, (6 folders); (7 folders) (Box III:155)
      - Books
      - Departments, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box III:156)
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies, (2 folders)
    - Summer
      - Articles, (5 folders); (7 folders) (Box III:157)
      - Books, (2 folders) (Box III:158)
      - Departments, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry (Box III:159)
      - Reader replies
    - Autumn
      - Articles, (4 folders); (6 folders) (Box III:160, Box III:161)
      - Books, (2 folders) (Box III:162)
      - Departments, (2 folders)
      - Dummy
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
  - 2001 (vol. 70) (Box III:163)
    - Winter
      - Articles, (10 folders)
      - Books
      - Departments, (2 folders)
      - Poetry (Box III:164)
      - Reader replies
    - Spring
      - Articles, (9 folders); (3 folders) (Box III:165)
      - Books, (3 folders)
      - Departments, (5 folders) (Box III:166)
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
    - Summer
      - Articles, (2 folders); (7 folders) (Box III:167)
      - Books
      - Departments, (2 folders) (Box III:168)
      - Miscellany
      - Reader replies
    - Autumn
      - Articles, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box III:169)
      - Books, (1 folder) (Box III:170)
      - Departments, (8 folders)
      - Miscellany
      - Reader replies (Box III:171)
  - 2002 (vol. 71)
    - Summer
      - Articles, (11 folders)
      - Books
      - Departments
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
  - 2003 (vol. 72)
    - Winter
      - Articles, (3 folders); (9 folders) (Box III:172)
      - Books, (2 folders) (Box III:173)
      - Departments, (8 folders)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders) (Box III:174)
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
    - Spring
      - Articles, (4 folders); (8 folders) (Box III:175)
      - Books
      - Departments, (5 folders) (Box III:176)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
      - Poetry
      - Reader replies
    - Summer (Box III:177)
      - Articles, (5 folders)
      - Books
      - Miscellany
      - Poetry
    - Autumn
      - Articles, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box III:178)
      - Books, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box III:179)
      - Departments, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
      - Poetry (Box III:180)
      - Reader replies